BRADLEY DILOLLO

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



316.250.6756



bldilollo@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/bradley-dilollo

PROFILE

Passionate, lifelong learner with a talent for quickly adapting to whatever is necessary. Motivated by meaningful, challenging work and excited to be part of a team that I can learn from and collaborate with. Experienced with interpersonal communication and adept at navigating the complexities of collaborative work.

SKILLS+LINKS

- Javascript
- React.js
- Node.js
- jQuery
- MySQL
- MongoDB
- Critical thinking
- Problem-solving

GitHub - github.com/bdilollo

References available upon request.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Software Development Bootcamp UC Berkeley Extension

September 2022 - December 2022

- Worked collaboratively and individually to learn and implement new technologies, solve complex problems, and think critically through solutions
- Developed, tested, and troubleshot projects that demonstrate proficiency in a wide array of technologies, including responsive user interfaces, RESTful APIs, and integrating with databases

Bachelor of Arts, English Sterling College (Sterling, KS)

August 2016 - May 2018

• Graduated with a 3.85 GPA, at the top of class within the department

EMPLOYMENT

Freelance Copywriter

October 2018 - Present

- Created work for a variety of organizations, with responsibilities ranging from articles and blog posts to fliers, brochures, letters, and email copy
- Wrote case statements, donation letters, board updates, and marketing material for a summer camp capital campaign, resulting in ~\$100k in small donations raised for new construction projects
- Communicated often and responded quickly to fluid deadlines and constantly changing demands

Crew - Trader Joe's

October 2020 - September 2022

- Managed large spreadsheets in order to track store order shipments, sales, and donations
- Responded quickly and creatively to a variety of needs as they developed, including balancing multiple tasks at a time
- Regularly worked with strict deadlines and under specific timelines, both individually and collaboratively
- Developed outstanding interpersonal skills--quickly developing rapport through small interactions and learning to work effectively with a wide variety of personalities and work styles